Guide to the Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Audio Recordings, 1963-2000, undated
  - Musical Recordings, 1963-1990, undated (Box 14)
    - Eno Experience, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Mark Epperson: Demo, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Stephanie Grosz: Junior Recital, 1984 Apr. 21, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Joey Howell: Demo, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 14)
    - Kneewalkers: Demo, 1984 Feb., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Lori Koenigsberg: Demo, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 14)
    - Ladyslipper, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Ladyslipper, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 14)
    - Dave Landers: Demo, 1983 Dec., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Dave Landers, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 14)
    - Dave Landers: Rough Mixes, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Warren Lankford, 1981 Apr. 7, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 14)
    - Warren Lankford: Demo, 1981 May, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - Warren Lankford: Voice, Piano Demos, 1981 May, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - Jim Legg: Disco Music, 1987 Nov. 22, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - Dan Locklair: Visions in the Haze, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - M M & L: Demo, 1983 July 10, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 16)
    - Martin: Demo, 1983 Aug., 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - Nat Martin, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Moods of Rhythm, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Music for Organ and Strings, 1964 Mar. 22, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - Vicki Oehling and Tom Funk: Demo, 1984 May, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 16)
    - One Real Band [sic]: Demo, 1980 Mar., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - One Real Band [sic]: Don't Kid Yourself, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - One Reel Band: Demo, reference dub, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Nancy Patterson: Senior Recital, 1990 Jan. 26, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Francis Perry: Page Auditorium, 1980 May 21, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Rainey Reel, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., 1 in. tape (Box 17)
    - Richard Rendleman, 1982 Jan., 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Richard Rendleman, Piano Demo #2, 1982 June, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Tilman Seebass, circa 1980-1990, 5 sound tape reels: 10 in.; 6 sound tape reels: 7 in. (Box 17)
    - She Loves Me, undated, 2 sound tape reels: 10 in. (Box 17)
    - Stormin' Norman & Suzy & the Frugtones: Black and Blue, 1980 July 25, 1 sound tape reel: 10 in. (Box 17)
    - W. Wallace, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - Bill Wilkerson: One Real Folly, undated, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 13)
    - X-Teens, 1980 Mar. 13, 1 sound tape reel: 7 in. (Box 17)
- Accession UA2009-0035
  - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, 2003 Oct. 3, DVCAM; a thank you to Nan Keohane (Box 18)
  - Duke Town Hall Meeting with Richard Brodhead: A Duke Conversation: Making a Difference, 2007 March 6, DVCAM, 2 tapes, multiple camera coverage, series held in Durham at Fuqua (Box 18)
  - Public Speech, Richard Brodhead, 2005 March 22, DVCAM, talk to undergraduates regarding student protests over fair wages/labor (Box 18)
  - John Hope Franklin Celebration of Life, 2009 June 11, DVCAM, master tape; CD, Vernon Jordan and President Bill Clinton speeches only (Box 18)
  - Duke Class of 2000, BetacamSP, montage of stills and music (Box 18)
  - French Science Center Dedication, 2007 Nov. 9, DVCAM, official ceremony (Box 18)
  - Campaign 2000 Debate, VHS, re: foreign policy (Box 18)
  - Converging and Diverging: Science & Humanities, 2005 Sept. 12, DVCAM, roundtable with Richard Brodhead (Box 18)
  - Price of Academic Freedom, 2004 Mar. 1, MiniDV, 2 tapes (Box 18)
  - Excerpts from Price of Academic Freedom, MiniDV, highlights (Box 18)
  - Genome Science and the Future of Medicine, 2005 Feb. 24, MiniDisc, audio recording by Dr. Huntington Willard and Dr. Geoffrey Ginsberg (Box 18)
- Accession UA2011-0007
  - Announcement of Richard H. Brodhead, New President of Duke University, Rare Book Room, cut version, undated, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Duke Children's Classic, Page Auditorium, edited show, 2000 May 19, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Kristina Johnson, Dean - Pratt School of Engineering, Interview, B-roll, 2003 June 16, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Provost Peter Lange, Remarks on Kristina Johnson, 2003 June 17, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, Tom's camera, 2005 April 20, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, Mike's camera, 2005 April 20, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, switched show, 2005 Oct. 11 (3 tapes), DVCAM (Box 19)
  - 17th Annual Service of Commemoration, MLK, 2006 Jan. 15 (2 tapes), DVCAM (Box 19)
  - DUMC 75th Special Nasher Dinner, 2006 Sept. 25, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Carl Rove, Page Auditorium, 2007 Dec. 3, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Deliberations, Griffith Theater, 2008 Oct. 24, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Soledad O'Brien, 2009 Jan. 22, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Convocation, Duke Chapel, 2009 Aug. 19, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Founder's Day, 2009 Oct. 1, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - Alumni War Memorial Dedication, 2009 Oct. 23, DVCAM (Box 19)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, 2005 April 20, MiniDV (Box 19)
  - DUMC 75th Special Nasher Dinner, B-roll, 2006 Sept. 25, MiniDV (Box 19)
  - A Conversation with Two Duke University Presidents: Nannerl Keohane and Richard Brodhead, moderated by Judy Woodruff, 2004 Feb. 1 (2 tapes), Betacam (Box 19)
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, walk from one to the other outside, 2005 Oct. 11, Betacam (Box 19)
  - President Richard Brodhead, Conversation with Gross Scholarship Recipients, 2006 Nov. 16 (2 tapes), Betacam (Box 19)
- Accession UA2014-0018
  - Duke Commencement Address - Ted Koppel, 1987 May 10, Umatic_0001 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement, 1992 May 17, Umatic_0002 (Box 20)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 1993 May 14, Umatic_0003 (Box 20)
  - Duke Spot #1, 1990s, BetacamSP_0001 (Box 20)
  - Duke Spot #2, 1990s, BetacamSP_0002 (Box 20)
  - Duke/JWT Spot, 1990s, BetacamSP_0003 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement Address, Marian Wright Edelman, 1992 May 14, BetacamSP_0004 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16, BetacamSP_0005 (Box 20)
  - Admissions Video - Duke Divinity School, circa 1993-1997, BetacamSP_0006 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Jimmy Carter, 1997 May 18, BetacamSP_0007 (Box 20)
  - Campaign For Duke Package, 1998 October 2, BetacamSP_0008 (Box 20)
  - College Is Possible, 1999 October 30, BetacamSP_0009 (Box 20)
  - College Is Possible, 1999 October 30, BetacamSP_0010 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Elizabeth Dole, 2000 May 14, BetacamSP_0011 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement, 1990 May 13, BetacamSP_0012 (Box 20)
  - The Inauguration of Nannerl O. Keohane, 1993 October 23, BetacamSP_0013 (Box 20)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16, BetacamSP_0014 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8, BetacamSP_0015 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8, BetacamSP_0016 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1995 May 14, BetacamSP_0017 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1995 May 14, BetacamSP_0018 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1996 May, BetacamSP_0019 (Box 21)
  - Lecture by John Ward Thomas, Chief of US Forestry Service, 1996 April 12, BetacamSP_0020 (Box 21)
  - Lecture by Kathleen A. McGinty, 1996 April 12, BetacamSP_0021 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1997 May 18, BetacamSP_0022 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1997 May 18, BetacamSP_0023 (Box 21)
  - Building Community: Conversations on Race with Robert Reich, 1997 November 17, BetacamSP_0024 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1998 May, BetacamSP_0025 (Box 21)
  - Duke Commencement, 1999 May, BetacamSP_0026 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2000 May 14, BetacamSP_0027 (Box 22)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2003 August 21, BetacamSP_0029 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8, BetacamSP_0028 (Box 22)
  - Service of Death and Rememberance for Dr. James H. Semans, 2005 April 26, BetacamSP_0031 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #1, 2005 May 13, BetacamSP_0032 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2005 May 14, BetacamSP_0033 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14, BetacamSP_0034 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2001 May 12, DVCAM_0001 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2001 November 4, DVCAM_0002 (Box 22)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2001 May 13, DVCAM_0003 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2002 May 11, DVCAM_0004 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2002 May 12, DVCAM_0005 (Box 22)
  - Duke Chapel - Palm/Passion Sunday Service, 2003 April 3, DVCAM_0006 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2003 May 11, DVCAM_0007 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8, DVCAM_0008 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8, DVCAM_0009 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2004 May 9, DVCAM_0010 (Box 22)
  - Duke Graduate School Convocation Service, 2004 August, DVCAM_0011 (Box 22)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2004 August 19, DVCAM_0012 (Box 22)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2005 May 14, DVCAM_0013 (Box 22)
  - Duke Commencement, 2005 May 15, DVCAM_0014 (Box 22)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2005 August 25, DVCAM_0015 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #3, 2006 May 13, DVCAM_0016 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14, DVCAM_0017 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14, DVCAM_0018 (Box 23)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2006 August 23, DVCAM_0019 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2007 May 12, DVCAM_0020 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2008 May 10, DVCAM_0021 (Box 23)
  - Duke Graduate School Graduation Ceremony, 2008 May 10, DVCAM_0022 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2008 May 11, DVCAM_0023 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - Fiona Terry, 2008 September 18, DVCAM_0024 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2009 May 9, DVCAM_0025 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2009 May 10, DVCAM_0026 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2009 May 10, DVCAM_0027 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Oprah Winfrey, 2009 May 10, DVCAM_0028 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2010 May 15, DVCAM_0029 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2010 May 16, DVCAM_0030 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2010 May 16, DVCAM_0031 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - Robert Gates in Page Auditorium, 2010 September 29, DVCAM_0032 (Box 23)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2010 September 30, DVCAM_0033 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - Jonathan Tisch in Griffith Film theater, 2010 October 19, DVCAM_0034 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - Temple Grandin in Baldwin Auditorium, 2011 February 21, DVCAM_0035 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - Jane Goodall in Page Auditorium, 2011 March 28, DVCAM_0036 (Box 23)
  - Duke Alumni Assocation - Duke B-ball Forum, 2011 April 8, DVCAM_0037 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2011 May 14, DVCAM_0038 (Box 23)
  - Pratt School of Engineering, 2011 May 15, DVCAM_0039 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2011 May 15, DVCAM_0040 (Box 23)
  - Did 9/11 Change Anything? Everything?, 2011 September 11, DVCAM_0041 (Box 23)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2011 September 22, DVCAM_0042 (Box 23)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2011 September 22, DVCAM_0043 (Box 23)
  - Lecture - General Martin Dempsey in Page Auditorium, 2012 January 12, DVCAM_0044 (Box 23)
  - "Seeds of Change Panel Discussion - Von Canon B, 2012 April 21, DVCAM_0045 (Box 23)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2012 May 12, DVCAM_0046 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 2012 May 13, DVCAM_0047 (Box 23)
  - MLK Address in Duke Chapel - Reverend William Turner, 2013 January 20, DVCAM_0048 (Box 23)
  - Celebrating The Past, Charting The Future, 2013 January 26, DVCAM_0049 (Box 23)
  - Freshman Convocation 2013, 2013 August 21, DVCAM_0050 (Box 23)
  - Duke Commencement, 1991 May 10, SVHS_0001 (Box 24)
  - Duke Commencement, 1992 May 17, SVHS_0002 (Box 24)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16, SVHS_0003 (Box 24)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8, SVHS_0004 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1997 May 17, SVHS_0005 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1998 May 16, SVHS_0006 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #1, 1999 May 14, SVHS_0007 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1999 May 15, SVHS_0008 (Box 24)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 1999 August 26, SVHS_0009 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2000 May 13, SVHS_0010 (Box 24)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2001 August 23, SVHS_0011 (Box 24)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2002 August 22, SVHS_0012 (Box 24)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 1991 May 10, VHS_0001 (Box 24)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 1997 August 28, VHS_0002 (Box 25)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2000 August 24, VHS_0003 (Box 25)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2005 August 25, VHS_0004 (Box 25)
  - Press Conference - Nobel Prize Winner Robert Lefkowitz, 2012 October 10, XDCAM_0001 (Box 25)
  - Lefkowitz-Brodhead Event in Griffith Film Theater, 2012 November 1, XDCAM_0002 (Box 25)